We'll have the invocation by Reverend of all sacred special church in this season.
Very soon as a wait.
Let us pray.
Almighty God, our Heavenly Father,
sinned down upon those who hold office in this town,
the spirit of wisdom, charity, and justice.
That was steadfast purpose.
They may faithfully serve in their offices
to promote the well-being of all people.
Through Jesus Christ, our Lord,
I'm in.
The Heavenly Father, the Star of the Lion,
the My Sight of the American,
and through the Reboot,
the Gorgitas Dance.
the Holy Land, the Holy Land,
the Lord, the Lord of the Litter to Jesus Jesus.
The Holy Land, the Lord of the Litter to Jesus.
Four Republican buttos,
get a personal pantose,
five,
I'm six times less for any old concrete most of the proof.
Is that.
I don't call.
Seven minutes from the June 17th, 2024.
Raise your head or me.
Motion to approve.
Hi.
Thank you.
Eight.
I'm a department of environmental quality amended permit number WT-00005821 073 for installation of this
infection for well number 7.
Yes, good evening board.
This is an agent nine or four.
The arpegrant that received for the new water tower on on 69A.
So the disinfection is actually the coronation system and then nine is the
unit.
So we're going to rate it out before we can bid it out.
We had to get a permit for EQ.
So this is our permit.
I'm free.
Reconstruction.
So we just as part of the permit we have to acknowledge it at the next meeting.
So there's no vote.
We're just acknowledging in the minutes that we received the permit.
So eight.
Eight nine.
No need of the.
The.
One.
You owe immediately now.
Cathedral.
A C Y I.
Now.
Okay.
The thank you.
This we.
Everything.
The.
K.
and the.
The.
all accessories.
We're taking a warm agreement, C-24-52, plus cold and cost, first national bank for the
purchase property on more of Main Street.
Sure, some marker trustees.
We saw some interest rates from five lending institutions in the area.
We had two nobids, the rates range from 5.90% down to 5.5% on 180 month turns or 15 years.
First national bank offer the lowest rate, 5.5, and this does require a payment plan to purchase.
We had Bank of Brand Lake, which was 5.9, which was 5.78 and first national 5.5, security
bank, and our best bank was the two that didn't bid, and we recommend setting up the
warm contract with first national.
This property is on North Main Street, which are approval.
Thank you.
Parker?
Hi.
The level of the agreement C-24-53, plus cold and cost for a cost of bank, the purchase
of property in North Main Street, and my amount.
This one is the same amount, same interest rates, everything's identical, and we need your approval
on this one as well.
Hi.
Thank you.
Thank you, Ron.
12.
Other divisions of any of which the residents have posted on this agenda, 13 staff reports, 14 trustee
community announcements, 15.
This meeting will be continued from Council chambers, remaining on the staff room for the
purpose of executive session at the place of agenda item number 6 of the regular meeting
of the MIPBAAA.